Student

Patrik Horny



About

I am a 21-year-old software engineering student from Slovakia who enjoys building websites. Currently I am doing my Bachelor in Software Engineering in Denmark. In my free time I developed an interest of learning about web development. Alongside learning how to code websites I learned a lot about visual hierarchy, main UI/UX principles, typography, mixing colors, animations, prototyping. From the technical side I learned how to better structure code, write semantic HTML, how to deploy website, SEO as well as some experience with e-commerce platform Shopify.

Besides web development I got a better grasp of how the process of developing a software looks like from ground up. For our projects we used Agile and for the managing a team we learned SCRUM where I took part as a SCRUM master.

Languages

English: C1

Slovak: Native speaker

Danish: A1

Experience

2019 - Present

Warehouse worker, Reitan Distribution

Checking product quality and quantity, packaging items, following safety regulations and protocols

2018 - 2019

Lifeguard, Thermal ŠÍRAVA SPA RESORT****

Maintenance of water conditions, enforcing safety rules and paying attention to swimmer activities and behavior

Education
August 2019 – August 2023
Software Engineering
VIA University College

Interests
Hitchhiking
Travelling
Photography
Video games
Gardening

Contact
Havnealle 47
8700, Horsens
+45 50 31 38 14
patriciushorny@gmail.com
https://www.patrikhorny.com/